JAMISON STRAMER

I am striving to strengthen myself both physically and spiritually; to grow and learn under those who have more experience than I. My goals are to become a truly strong and independent man. I understand every moment is another in which I can continue to learn and grow.

EXPERIENCE

08/2011 - 05/2012

LAUNCH STUDENT, HIDDEN ACRES CHRISTIAN CENTER

In 2012 I graduated from LAUNCH leadership training. During LAUNCH I grew immensely. I learned the basics on how and when to lead and I gained understanding of a work-ethic. I was able to expand my breadth of knowledge on many things. I was given the opportunity to us many different types of tools and machines. One day I would be in the kitchen and bakery the next out at the log splitter and even the next working on constructing a building. In as far as leadership goes we, the LAUNCH students, where in charge of keeping the Beyond Helpers (helpful high school students) on task and to train them.

We each had an end-of-program project requirement. This project could be anything we personally felt would be useful to the campground. I chose to build a hiking trail and picnic spot near the lake. I sold the idea to the camp head and explained to him why it would be of great use. After receiving the go-ahead from him I got to work. I built a floating dock and carved out a trail on the far side of the lake. In recent years other workers and taken my idea and groundwork and grew it larger. A hammock haven, a fishing and picnic spot and a hiking and hunting trail have grown out of the work I had done.

06/2012 - 05/2016

SHIFT MANAGER, OLD COUNTRY BUFFET

- Started as a Floor Server
- Had the opportunity to become a baker and a dishwasher in order to accumulate more hours per week
- I was promoted to Shift Supervisor after a little under two years
- Other positions I do regularly are cooking, food stocking, cashiering, and talking to guests
- I learned how to effectively solve problems

02/2016 - PRESENT

MATERIAL HANDLER, MECHANICAL ASSEMBLER, PM3 TECHNOLOGIES

- Installing of plumbing inside machines
- Installing of Electrical boxes and electrical components inside machines
- Bringing inventory to congruency with the material lists
- Forklift operator
- Inventory Restructuring
- Misc. Construction

- Metal refinishing
- Shipping and Receiving
- Technical Writer
- Reading/redlining prints

EDUCATION

2013-2015

UNDERGRAD(INCOMPLETE), ANOKA TECHNICAL COLLEGE

Earned 31 credits towards an undergraduate degree in Information Technology Management.

2019-2020

FULL STACK FLEX PROGRAM(IN PROGRESS), UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA

Earned the skills necessary to thrive in the world of Web Development. Built a Portfolio to prove of my ability to succeed in this capability.

SKILLS

- Leadership training through LAUNCH Leadership
- Leadership experience through being promoted to Shift Manager at Old Country Buffet
- Food Service experience (Cook and Dishwasher, Baker, Meat Prep)
- Microsoft Office experience (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, OneNote, Outlook, Access)
- Construction experience (Wood Cutting, Insulation, Wiring, Plumbing, Siding, Dry-wall, Tiling, and Painting.)
- Yard work experience (Two types of Mowers, three types of weed whippers, Hydraulic log splitter, and Chainsaws)
- Customer experience (Cashiering, Hotel maintenance, and Food service server)
- Web Development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node, Git, Java)
- Database Organization (Data-entry, Inventory Restructuring and Re-assigning)
- Technical Writing Ability (No Degree)

ACTIVITIES

- Theology
- Hunting
- Fishing
- Technology of all kinds
- History
- Science
- TTRPG
- I actively pursue knowledge of all kinds